# Austin Rowe Web Developer

(205)-807-4715

amrowe2018@gmail.com

https://github.com/Austin-Rowe

# **Skills**

- React
- Redux
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Node/Express
- PostgreSQL
- AWS

# **Notable Experience**

# Iris Global Harvest School of Missions

The Harvest School is a 3 month school in Pemba, Mozambique. It includes an optional extended outreach that I went on into the Middle East for 2 weeks. This was an incredible experience that gave me a deep passion for missions and seeing the lost reached.

## **Projects**

### RugZilla

Ecommerce site created with React, Redux, Node, Express, Paypal, and AWS. You can check it out here.

#### hireAustinRowe.com

Portfolio site created with React.

#### **Chrome Extension**

Chrome extension created using vanilla JS, DOM manipulation, and OOJ. Can be viewed <u>here.</u>

## **Work History**

**United Textiles** Retail Associate

December 2015 - Present

#### Whole Foods Market Cashier

May 2015 - October 2015

Zaxby's Cook/Cashier

August 2014 - May 2015

Chick-fil-A Cashier

June 2012 - August 2014

## **Education**

#### **Team TreeHouse Front-End Developer Track**

January 2018 - March 2018

Node, SQL, & PostgreSQL - Mastering Backend Web Development

May 2018

**SQL & PostgreSQL for Beginners** 

**April 2018** 

#### **Hoover High School**

**Graduated May 2015**